LAB-3: Ojective
 
	1	HTML
	a	Modify the READ.me
	b	Top 10 ordered list in HTML
	c	Education summary to an unordered list
	2	JS
	a	Add 6th q, takes numeric input, prompt users to guess the number
	b	An alert that says too high or too low
	c	4 opportunities to guess the correct number
	d	After 4 tell the correct answer. Consider using loop
	3	Still JS
	a	Add 7th q, multiple possible correct answer that are stored in an array.
	b	Give the user 6 attempts.
	c	Give them after 6th attempt
	d	Display all the correct answers.
	e	Use loops
	4	Final Score
	a	Keep track of total number of correct answers.
	b	At the end tell them how many they got correct out of 7.
	5	Use Lighthouse.
	a	50-65 acceptable.
	b	Add the screenshot of your score to the READ.me
	6	Use console.log of the prompts
	7	Add CSS & HTML
 
STRETCH GOAL
	1	DRY code. Use arrays, for loops.
	2	Use math.random
	3	After achieving MVP can use
	4	.includes() and .join()
